Tell me now!
Where is the vault?
Release Mu Ying first.
Do you think I'm negotiating with you?
You old bastard.
Do you think I'm just someone you can kill
or kidnap whenever you want?
And you still want to know the vault's location?
Even if I knew, I wouldn't tell you.
You old bastard!
Mu Ying!
I thought I'd never see you again.
I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm so glad you're okay.
Alright, alright, alright.
I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Look.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm just glad you're okay.
Not for kids.
How did you escape?
He locked me in that granary by the river.
There happened to be a hidden door inside,
so I smashed it open.
A flimsy little warehouse
thought it could hold me?
And releasing poison gas?
Pah!
You are so vicious.
You old bastard.
Right, right, right.
You inhaled the poison gas.
Let's hurry to the hospital.
Wait, wait.
Don't worry.
I didn't inhale it.
When he released the poison gas,
I held my breath.
I barely breathed in any.
I'm fine.
I really didn't.
I'm fine, look.
Impressive.
I'm glad you're okay.
I'll cuff him first.
Okay.
Master,
you worried for nothing.
She just smashed her way out on her own.
By the way, Mu Ying,
we found the location of the vault.
What do we do next?
Next,
we'll go take a look first.
Let's see the vault he schemed so hard for.
Once we find it,
I'll notify the Cultural Relics Bureau to take over.
Where is it?
Sihua Street, North Alley.
I've never heard of this place.
It might be
based on an ancient map.
We'll find out once we look up the address.
Alright.
You guys go research the info,
and I'll take him back to the police station.
Okay.
Be careful.
Let's go.
Move.
Congratulations, Ms. Mu Ying,
on officially becoming Police Chief of Lijia Town Police Station.
Good morning, Police Chief.
Morning, good morning.
Stop talking nonsense.
What's going on?
Why is everyone here today?
Congratulations, Police Chief Mu Ying.
Because you solved the relic theft case,
and caught the Yanbei Master Thief,
Director Wu of the Provincial Bureau issued your Letter of Appointment.
You're officially promoted.
You are now the official Police Chief.
I...
I'm officially promoted?
Yes.
I'm officially promoted!
Yes, Police Chief.
I've become the Police Chief!
If only my Dad knew.
Mu Gui was convicted of dereliction of duty
and sentenced to five years.
He's currently serving time in prison.
Police Chief Mu,
to tell you the truth,
you're more righteous than your Dad.
You are decisive and resolute.
You're even tougher than us men.
We will all follow your orders from now on.
All officers of Lijia Town Police Station
await the Police Chief's orders!
Await the Police Chief's orders!
Mu Ying.
What is it?
The former Sihua Street, North Alley
corresponds to the location of
the present-day Hu Port.
The vault should be located right there.
Then let's go!
But this...
They...
Everyone is here today.
Keep this safe.
Let's go.
Okay.
Dismissed!
I compared the ancient and modern maps.
Actually, the location of the vault
is right here.
No.
Are you sure about this?
The vault is here?
But where is it?
There was a flood the year before last.
They opened the canal to release the water.
The vault
was submerged at the bottom of the river.
The so-called Sihua Street, North Alley
actually refers to this place.
You mean,
the vault sank to the bottom of the river?
Master,
are the treasures inside still there?
The current is rapid.
The treasures must have been washed away.
Benefactor Li grew greedy for the Golden Tomb.
He killed his three accomplices
to keep the gold to himself.
To keep this secret safe,
he also killed
Elder Ding and his grandson, who lived at the Golden Tomb's exit.
He was blinded by greed
and murdered five people.
It's unforgivable.
The Old Newsvendor,
in order to monopolize the vault
and escape the law,
Put this on.
had his accomplice, the Spirit Medium,
poison Benefactor Li to death.
Then,
he poisoned the Spirit Medium too.
Plus the three innocent wives
and Mengzhu who died tragically.
Two vaults.
Eleven lives.
All of these sins
stem from an obsession with ill-gotten wealth.
The heaviest shackles in the world
aren't money itself,
but the obsession with ill-gotten wealth.
The vanity built by money
will eventually, under the light of conscience,
vanish into nothing.
As the saying goes,
All conditioned phenomena
are like dreams, illusions, bubbles, and shadows.
That's right.
My Dad was also driven by greed,
and let Benefactor Li go.
Now he's a prisoner.
I have to go back and see him.
What are you doing here?
Dad.
I made you some dumplings.
Eat them while they're hot.
You're the one who turned me in.
And you have the nerve to show up.
The remains of Elder Ding and his grandson
have been found at the bottom of the river.
Benefactor Li has also confessed.
He committed countless crimes and was poisoned to death.
If you hadn't let him go back then,
these revenge murders wouldn't have happened.
I reported you
because I didn't want to see
people like Chunmei have nowhere to turn for justice.
I reported you.
Was I wrong?
Way too salty. Are you trying to kill me with salt?
Did you kill the salt merchant?
Eat it or don't.
You're so hard to please.
Stop right there.
I haven't died from the salt yet.
You didn't even bring a bowl of soup with you.
I'll go buy you some.
Dad.
Dad!
I became the Police Chief!
I want some lotus root and pork rib soup.
Got it.
Print 500 more copies of Heavenly Craftsmanship.
The book has 209 pages.
That'll be 100 silver dollars in total.
Excuse me.
You got it wrong.
This book...
should have 210 pages.
Master.
How did you know that?
Heavenly Craftsmanship
is the most important book in our library.
Of course I know it inside out.
It only has 209 pages.
The last page was torn out.
We don't have enough money.
We're short by 20.
Sir.
How about this?
Start printing it for me first.
When it's time to settle the bill,
I'll pay you the remaining 20.
Okay.
Alright, thank you.
Master.
That's 20 we're talking about.
Have some faith in yourself.
With your eloquence,
with three days of storytelling,
you can easily earn that 20, right?
I earn it?
What?
Why do I have to earn it?
Did you take our experience in Lijia Town
and turn it into a story script?
Smart.
So, my Master,
with his ability of Five Senses Deduction,
solved a wrongful case.
Just recently,
he took a stroll outside the Li family's gold shop
and perfectly reconstructed
the full story of the Li family gold shop burglary.
It turns out,
the night watchman was a spy for a gang of thieves.
They poisoned a wealthy family's bride.
After killing her, they impersonated the King of Hell
and stole the bride's corpse.
They also took all the gold jewelry
from the Li family's gold shop
that the bride's corpse was wearing.
They even spread rumors about
the King of Hell's Wedding
to divert the police's attention.
In reality,
what this gang of thieves
really wanted to steal
was the gold shop of the richest man, Benefactor Li.
But no matter how resourceful the thieves were,
they couldn't escape my Master's keen eyes.
Jiang Huai.
I know what caused your hallucinations.
Come with me.
They also made up the Five Ghosts Carrying Wealth story to disrupt the case.
Doctor.
It's just that...
After the fire in our family's library,
my eyes
became very strange.
I keep seeing unusual things.
He takes forever to explain.
He keeps having hallucinations.
Doctor, what's wrong with him?
The smoke from the fire
damaged part of your retinas,
causing your eyes
to lose some visual function.
As a result,
your brain
will, within your field of vision,
automatically generate imaginary images.
So it's an eye disease
causing visual hallucinations.
Yes.
You don't need to worry too much about it.
After taking some medication,
your retinas will heal on their own.
Thank you.
No problem.
See, I told you.
It was all in your head.
Don't think about it anymore.
But...
that's not right.
Elder Ding and Xiaobao...
they are real.
You've never seen them.
How could you imagine them?
The newspaper.
I saw them in the newspaper.
Master.
What character is this?
Oh, this one?
This is "ni".
It means to drown.
Grandfather and Grandson in Lijia Town Drown After Accidental Fall.
How pitiful.
Look here.
Xiaobao, don't run around.
Xiaobao!
Be careful not to fall.
So nice.
Police Chief.
A telegram from the Provincial Bureau.
A murder involving evil Zhuyou Sorcery happened in Wu City.
They want you to go to Wu City to assist with the investigation.
Wu City.
I've heard about the case in Wu City.
Several people died from being possessed.
No murder weapon.
No witnesses.
Many villagers were so scared they moved away.
It's completely bizarre.
Police Chief,
you can't go!
It's quite interesting.
I'll go to Wu City and see for myself.
As for you,
stay in Lijia Town.
Keep things in order.
Keep up the good work.
I'm off.
Don't worry, Police Chief.
She-devil!
Why is it you again?
This can't be good.
It's good news.
The Provincial Bureau...
...wants me to investigate a Zhuyou Sorcery murder in Wu City.
The three of us should go together.
What do you say?
I'm applying medicine to my eyes.
I'm not going.
I'm not going either.
You never feed us...
...and you always boss me around.
This time is different.
I'll cover your room, board, and everything else.
I also heard...
...that over in Wu City...
...is the last page of Heavenly Craftsmanship.
If you don't want to go, forget it.
I'll just go by myself.
In that case...
Off to Wu City!
Let's go! Let's go!
They set off to investigate the strange Zhuyou Sorcery case.
The journey ahead is long...
...and full of unknown dangers.
Dear audience,
the tale of the strange mansion in Lijia Town...
...comes to a close here.
As the saying goes,
What goes around comes around.
A snake trying to swallow an elephant.
To find out what happens next...
...stay tuned for the next chapter.
Bravo!
Wonderful! Good! Good!
Fantastic!